Guide to the Records of the Office of External Affairs, Commencement and Special Events RG.7.4
New York University Archives
- Series II: Publications, 1956-2024; 15 Linear Feet in 1 record carton, 3 flat boxes, 2 manuscript boxes, 1 oversize flat box, and 9 boxes without container profiles.; 5 audiocassettes
  - King of Spain Dinner R.S.V.P., December 6, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - AmeriCorps: Project Safety Net, Fall 1984 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Sir Steven Runciman Convocation, October 18, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Gala Dinner Dance, November 3, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Reverend Iakovos Convocation, November 25, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Winter Celebration, March 2, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Ral Alfonsin Convocation, March 21, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - New York University Development Campaign, September 1985 - August 1988 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Shimon Peres Convocation, October 21, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 2, Box Shared University Archives 002, Reel 6)
  - Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences 50th Anniversary, October 22, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Academic Convocation: Dr. Alfred Gottschalk, October 28, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Alumni Night, March 22, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - The Time Award: Corazon Aquino, September 18, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Alumni Night, November 15, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - NYU Magazine, 1986-1991 (Box 34, Folder 4-7)
  - Milton Petrie Lecture, February 26, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Milton Petrie Lecture In Entrepreneurship, March 10, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Alexander Onassis Center for Hellenic Studies, March 1987 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Alexander Onassis Center for Hellenic Studies, November 13, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Spring Celebration, April 4, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Leonard Stern Hall Dedication, May 1987 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - NYU Alumni Cruise, September 18, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - All-University Dinner Dance, October 22, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - All-University Dinner Dance, October 20, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - All-University Dinner Dance, November 8, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - All University Dinner Dance, November 7, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - All University Dinner Dance, October 22, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Special Convocation: David Kriser Central Center, November 18, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - All Libraries Convocation Samples, December 15, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Second Annual Spring Celebration, April 20, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Special Academic Convocation: Franois Mitterand, September 20, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Special Academic Celebration: Alexander Onassis, October 10, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - NYU in Albany Day, February 27, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Giulio Andreotti Special Convocation, March 8, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Rita Sssmuth Lecture "The Future of Europe", March 19, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Prime Minister Toshiki Kaifu of Japan Special Convocation, September 28, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - President Carlos Salinas of Mexico Special Convocation, October 1, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Casa Italiana Zerilli-Marimo Dedication, November 13, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - 33 Third Avenue, Alumni Hall Brochure, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Alumni in Florida, January 19, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Classroom Dedication, September 20, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Havel Convocation, October 27, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Prime Minister Albert Reynolds Luncheon, September 15, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Ireland House Dedication, April 26, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 4, Box 38, Folder 39)
  - Annual Picnic Sample Information, October 2, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Gallatin Convocation, October 12, 1995 (Box 36, Folder 6, Box 38, Folder 40)
  - President Kim Young-sam Convocation Programs, October 23, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 5-6)
- Series III: Commencement, 1834-2024; 31.5 Linear Feet in 4 record cartons, 47 manuscript boxes, 2 flat boxes, 1 oversize flat box, and 52 boxes without container profiles.; 6 audiocassettes; 15.6 Megabytes in 13 computer files
  This series includes paper files and audio recordings for New York University's Commencement, Baccalaureate, and related events dating from 1834 to 2019. Files typically contain programs, invitations, tickets, rosters, event schedules, and speaker lists. Event scripts, librettos, and instructions in this series provided guidance for those who presented and participated in the various ceremonies. Alternate plans for inclement weather and other scenarios are also in this series. This series also contains handwritten addresses from NYU's early Commencement ceremonies, and printed copies of many of addresses given by NYU Presidents, Deans, and guests over the years. Special Commencement edition issues of the NYU Bulletin included copies of Commencement and Baccalaureate addresses, schedules, and rosters of graduating students. Planning correspondence, post-event analysis notes, and dressing instructions for student and faculty are also in this series. A small collection of audio recordings and collectible items related to Grad Alley are also in this series. Commencement ephemera for some of NYU's schools and divisions is also in this series including the Law School, Medical School, and Steinhardt School. General planning files from the 1970s and 1980s refer to specific tasks, including commencement stage and canopy design, and designs for new banners and logos for graduation robes.
  - Program, Ticket, 1834 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Program, 1835 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Program, Handwritten Address, Ticket, 1836-10-05 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Program, Ticket, 1837 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Program, Handwritten Address, Ticket, 1838 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Program, 1839 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Ticket, 1840 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Program, Handwritten Address, Ticket, 1841 (Box 56, Folder 8-9)
  - Program, Ticket, 1842 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Program, Ticket, 1844 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Programs, 1844-1945 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Program, Invitation, Ticket, 1845 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Programs, Tickets, 1846-1852 (Box 56, Folder 14-21)
  - Programs, 1852-1853 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Programs, Tickets, 1853-1854 (Box 57, Folder 2-3)
  - Program, Invitation, 1855 (Box 57, Folder 4-5)
  - Program, Invitation, Ticket, 1856 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Program, Ticket, 1857 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Bound Programs, 1857-1868 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Program, Ticket, 1858 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Programs, Invitations, Tickets, 1859-1860 (Box 57, Folder 10-11)
  - School of Law -- Commencement Ephemera, 1860-1899 (Box 99, Folder 1-26)
  - Programs, Tickets, 1861-1862 (Box 57, Folder 12-13)
  - Programs, Invitations, Tickets, 1863-1864 (Box 57, Folder 14-15)
  - Programs, Tickets, 1865-1866 (Box 57, Folder 16-17)
  - Program, Invitation, Ticket, 1867 (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Programs, Tickets, 1868-1869 (Box 57, Folder 19-20)
  - Bellevue Hospital Medical College -- Commencement Ephemera, 1869-1884 (Box 99, Folder 30-43)
  - Program, Invitation, Ticket, 1870 (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - Program, Invitation, 1871 (Box 57, Folder 22-23)
  - Programs, Tickets, 1872-1873 (Box 57, Folder 24-25)
  - Program, Invitation, 1874 (Box 57, Folder 26)
  - Programs, 1874-1875 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Program, Invitation, 1875 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Program, Speaker List, 1876 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Program, Ticket, 1877 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Program, Speaker List, Invitation, 1878 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Programs, Invitations, 1879-1880 (Box 58, Folder 6-7)
  - Program, Speaker List, 1881 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Program, 1882 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Program, Invitation, Addresses, 1883 (Box 58, Folder 10-11)
  - Program, Invitation, 1884 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Program, 1885 (Box 58, Folder 13-14)
  - Program, Invitation, Ticket, 1886 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Bellevue Hospital Medical College -- Commencement Ephemera, 1886-1899, 1919, 1932-1936 (Box 99, Folder 44-54)
  - Programs, 1886-1893 (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Programs, Invitations, 1887-1888 (Box 58, Folder 17-18)
  - Program, Invitation, Ticket, 1889 (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - Programs, Invitations, 1890-1891 (Box 58, Folder 20-21)
  - Program, Invitation, Ticket, 1892 (Box 58, Folder 22)
  - Program, 1893 (Box 58, Folder 23)
  - Program, Invitation, 1894 (Box 58, Folder 24)
  - Program, Invitation, Ticket, 1895 (Box 58, Folder 25, Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Program, Event Calendar, Invitation, Ticket, 1896 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Program, Event Calendar, Ticket, Letter to NYU Faculty re: Speeches, 1897 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Programs, 1897-1900 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Program, Invitation, Ticket, 1898 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Programs, Event Calendars, Invitations, Tickets, 1899-1903 (Box 59, Folder 6-10)
  - Baccalaureate Service and Commencement Programs, Ephemera, 1904 (Box 60, Folder 1-2)
  - Baccalaureate Service Programs, 1904-1936 (Box 60, Item 3)
  - Program, Invitation, Ticket, 1905 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Program, Event Calendar, Invitation, Ticket, 1906 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Baccalaureate Service and Commencement Programs, Ephemera, 1907-1908 (Box 60, Folder 6-8)
  - Program, Invitations, 1909 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Baccalaureate Service and Commencement Programs, Ephemera, 1910 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Program, Invitation, 1911 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Baccalaureate Service and Commencement Programs, Proposed Plan, Ephemera, 1912-1913 (Box 61, Folder 2-3)
  - Baccalaureate Service and Commencement Programs, Instructions, Ephemera, 1914 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Baccalaureate Service and Commencement Programs, Addresses, Ephemera, 1915 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Baccalaureate Service and Commencement Programs, Instructions, Planning, 1916 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Baccalaureate Service and Commencement Programs, Bulletin, Print Communication re: War Service Announcement, Gift of Ambulance in Honor of the Class, 1917 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Baccalaureate Service and Commencement Programs, Address, Roll of Honor, Instructions, 1918 (Box 61, Folder 8-9)
  - Commencement Message to Students in Military Service, 1918 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Address, 1918 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Baccalaureate Service and Commencement Programs, Address, Instructions, Ephemera, 1919 (Box 62, Folder 1-2)
  - Baccalaureate Service and Commencement Programs, Event Calendar, 1920 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Programs, 1920-1929 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Baccalaureate Service and Commencement Programs, Address, Ephemera, 1921 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - College of Dentistry -- Commencement Programs, Ephemera, Instructions, 1921-2001 (Box 96, Folder 1-8)
  - Baccalaureate Service and Commencement Programs, Address, Ephemera, Instructions, 1922 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Baccalaureate Service and Commencement Programs, Addresses, 1923 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Baccalaureate Service and Commencement Programs, Address, Event Calendar, 1924 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Baccalaureate Service and Commencement Programs, Addresses, Ephemera, Instructions, 1925 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Baccalaureate Service and Commencement Programs, Addresses, Event Calendar, 1926 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Addresses, 1923-1929 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Bound Commencement and Baccalaureate Addresses and Bulletins, 1923-1953 (Box 94, Item 1-2)
  - Baccalaureate Service and Commencement Programs, Addresses, Ephemera, 1927-1929 (Box 63, Folder 3-5)
  - Addresses, 1930, 1933-1939 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Program, 1930 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Baccalaureate Service and Commencement Programs, Addresses, Ephemera, 1930-1931 (Box 64, Folder 1-3)
  - Programs, 1930-1935 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Baccalaureate Service and Commencement Programs, Bulletin, Addresses, Ephemera, 1932-1937 (Box 64, Folder 4-7, Box 65, Folder 1-4)
  - Program, 1934 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - College of Fine Arts -- Commencement Program, 1934 (Box 96, Folder 12)
  - School of Law -- Commencement Ephemera, 1934, 1976-1987 (Box 99, Folder 27-29)
  - Bellevue School of Nursing -- Commencement Address, 1935 (Box 96, Folder 9)
  - Baccalaureate Service Programs, 1937-1968 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Programs, Bulletins, Ephemeras, 1938-1939 (Box 65, Folder 6-7)
  - Programs, 1938-1939 (Box 39, Folder 7-8)
  - Programs, Bulletins, 1940-1942 (Box 66, Folder 1-3)
  - Addresses, 1940-1942 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Programs, 1940-1942 (Box 39, Folder 10-12)
  - Baccalaureate Service and Commencement Programs, Bulletin, Ephemera, Addresses, 1943 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Bulletin, 1943 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - College of Engineering -- Commencement Program, 1943 (Box 96, Folder 10)
  - College of Medicine -- Commencement Ephemera, 1943, 1964, 1970-1987 (Box 99, Folder 55-58)
  - Program, 1944 (Box 39, Folder 14, Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Program, Bulletin, Ticket, Instructions, 1945 (Box 66, Folder 6-7)
  - Bulletin, 1945 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Bulletin, 1946 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Program, 1946 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Program, Ticket, Addresses, 1946-1947 (Box 67, Folder 1-2)
  - Program, Addresses, 1947-1949 (Box 39, Folder 18-21, Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Program, Tickets, Invitation, Addresses, 1949 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Program, Bulletin, Libretto, 1950 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Bulletin, 1950 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Program, 1950 (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Program, 1951 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Baccalaureate Service and Commencement Programs, Bulletin, 1951-1954 (Box 67, Folder 6, Box 68, Folder 1-3)
  - Program, Bulletin, 1952 (Box 39, Folder 25-26)
  - Program, Bulletin, 1953 (Box 39, Folder 27-28)
  - Program, Bulletin, 1954 (Box 39, Folder 29-30)
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1954 (Box 39, Folder 31)
  - Commencement Program, Bulletin, Luncheon Seating List, Address, 1955 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Program, Bulletin, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 32-33)
  - Program, Bulletin, 1956 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Program, Bulletin, 1956 (Box 39, Folder 34-35)
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1956 (Box 39, Folder 36)
  - Baccalaureate Service and Commencement Programs, Bulletin, Dissertations List, 1957 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Program, Bulletin, 1957 (Box 39, Folder 37-38)
  - Program, Bulletin, 1958 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Program, Bulletin, 1958 (Box 39, Folder 39-40)
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1958 (Box 39, Folder 41)
  - Program, Bulletin, 1959 (Box 39, Folder 42-43)
  - Program, Bulletin, Libretto, 1959 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1959 (Box 39, Folder 44)
  - Program, Bulletin, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 45-46)
  - Commencement Program, Bulletin, Tickets, Libretto, 1960 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 47)
  - Program, Bulletin, 1961 (Box 40, Folder 1-2)
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1961 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Commencement Program, Bulletin, 1961 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Program, Bulletin, 1962 (Box 40, Folder 4-5)
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1962 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Baccalaureate Service and Commencement Programs, Bulletin, Libretto, Instructions, Ephemera, 1962-1964 (Box 69, Folder 2-7)
  - Programs, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Baccalaureate and Commencement Programs, Ephemera, Bulletin, Instructions / Scripts, 1964 (Box 69, Folder 6-7)
  - Program, Bulletin, 1964 (Box 40, Folder 9-10)
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1964 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Baccalaureate Service and Commencement Programs, Ephemera, Addresses, Bulletin, 1965 (Box 70, Folder 1-3)
  - Programs, 1965 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1965 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Baccalaureate Service and Commencement Programs, Ephemera, Bulletin, Instructions, Libretto, 1966 (Box 70, Folder 4-5)
  - Program, Bulletin, 1966 (Box 40, Folder 14-15)
  - Programs, 1966 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1966 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Program, Bulletin, 1967 (Box 40, Folder 17-18)
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1967 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Baccalaureate Service and Commencement Programs, Ephemera, Bulletin, Addresses, Instructions, 1967 (Box 70, Folder 6, Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Baccalaureate Service and Commencement Programs, Ephemera, Bulletin, Addresses, Instructions, 1968 (Box 71, Folder 2-4)
  - Programs, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Baccalaureate Service and Commencement Programs, Ephemera, Bulletin, Addresses, Instructions, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 5-6)
  - Program, Bulletin, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 22-23)
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Planning Files, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - Commencement Speech "Convocation for Peace", 1970 (Box 53, Audiocassette 7_4_001)
  - Bulletin, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - Baccalaureate Service and Commencement Programs, Ephemera, Bulletin, Addresses, Instructions, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 7-8)
  - Graduate School of Business Administration -- Pre-Commencement Exercises Program, 1970s-1980s (Box 96, Folder 13-14)
  - Baccalaureate Service and Commencement Programs, Ephemera, Bulletin, Addresses, Instructions, 1971 (Box 72, Folder 1-3)
  - Program, 1971 (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - Baccalaureate Ceremony, 1971 (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - Program, Bulletin, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 30-31)
  - Program, Ephemera, Bulletin, Addresses, 1972 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Program, Ephemera, Bulletin, Addresses, Instructions, 1973 (Box 72, Folder 5-6)
  - Program, Bulletin, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 32-33)
  - Planning Files, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 34-35)
  - Programs, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 36)
  - Program, Ephemera, Bulletin, Addresses, Instructions, Publicity, 1974 (Box 73, Folder 1-3)
  - Planning Files -- Madison Square Garden Logistics, 1974-1988 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - University Without Walls -- Commencement Program, 1974-1976 (Box 96, Folder 11)
  - Program, Bulletin, Addresses, Instructions, 1975 (Box 73, Folder 4-6)
  - Programs, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 37)
  - Programs, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 38)
  - Program, Ephemera, Addresses, Libretto, Roster, 1976 (Box 74, Folder 1-2)
  - Program, Ephemera, Addresses, Instructions, Scripts, Roster, 1977 (Box 74, Folder 3-5)
  - Program, Ticket, Roster, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 39-41)
  - Program, Roster, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 42-43)
  - Commencement Program, Ephemera, Addresses, Instructions, Roster, 1978 (Box 74, Folder 6-7)
  - Planning Files -- Creation of Banners and Logos Correspondence, Mock-ups, Images, 1978-1988 (Box 55, Folder 6-7)
  - Planning Files -- Stage and Canopy Design / Plans, 1978-1987 (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Program, Ephemera, Addresses, Libretto, Instructions, Roster, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 1-3)
  - Program, Roster, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 44-45)
  - Program, Roster, Parking Permit, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 46-48)
  - Program, Ephemera, Addresses, Planning Correspondence, Roster, Dean's Postcard Message, 1980 (Box 75, Folder 4-5, Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Gallatin Division -- Commencement Programs, 1980s, 1995 (Box 96, Folder 15)
  - Even-song Sheet Music, Notes, Drafts, Versions, 1980-2006 (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - Program, Addresses, Roster, 1981 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Program, Roster, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 49-50)
  - Program, Roster, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 51-52)
  - Program, Ephemera, Addresses, Roster, Instructions, Correspondence, 1982 (Box 75, Folder 7-8, Box 76, Folder 1-2, Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Program, Addresses, Roster, Instructions, Correspondence, 1983 (Box 76, Folder 3-5, Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Program, Roster, Park Permits, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 53-56)
  - Academic Attire Insignia Creation, Ordering, Placement Instructions, Mock-up Samples, 1983-1984, undated (Box 93, Folder 9-11)
  - Program, Roster, Park Permit, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 1-3)
  - Fountain Seating and Park Meetings, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Park: Agenda Notes and Permit, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Program, Ephemera, Addresses, Instructions, Planning Correspondence, Roster, 1984 (Box 76, Folder 6-8, Box 77, Folder 1, Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Baccalaureate and Commencement Programs, Addresses, Roster, Ephemera, Instructions, Rain Plans, Press Kit, 1985 (Box 77, Folder 2-7, Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Program, Roster, Park Permit, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 6-8)
  - Program, Roster, Park Permit, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 9-11)
  - Program, Addresses, Roster, Ephemera, Instructions, 1986 (Box 78, Folder 1-7, Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Alumni Association Recognition Certificates, 1986 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Programs, Addresses, Roster, Ephemera, Instructions, Planning and Post-Event Correspondence, 1987 (Box 78, Folder 8-10, Box 79, Folder 1-6, Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Program, Roster, 1987 (Box 41, Folder 12-13)
  - Commencement Ceremony, October 22, 1987 (Box 53, Audiocassette 7_4_015 -- 7_4_016)
  - Program, Roster, 1988 (Box 41, Folder 14-15)
  - Program, Ephemera, Addresses, Roster, Rain Plan, Instructions, Planning and Post-Event Correspondence, 1988 (Box 79, Folder 7-11)
  - Commencement Ceremony, October 20, 1988 (Box 53, Audiocassette 7_4_019)
  - Program, Roster, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 16-17)
  - Scripts, Press Kit, 1989 (Box 81, Folder 9-10)
  - Program, Roster, Ephemera, Scripts, Instructions, Planning Correspondence, 1989 (Box 80, Folder 1-5)
  - Program, Ephemera, Instructions, Planning Correspondence, 1990 (Box 80, Folder 6-7)
  - Program, Planning, Script, Rain Script, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 18-22)
  - Alumni Brunch, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Romich Memos, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Staff, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Set up, Maps, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Requisitions, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Instructions to Marshals -- Entrance, Guest Seating, Live TV, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Instructions to Students Procession Marshals, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - Programs, Planning Files, Script, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 30-32)
  - Abbreviated Park Script (Drizzle), Rain Script, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 33-34)
  - Alumni Brunch, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 35)
  - Memos, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 36)
  - Set-up, Maps, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 37)
  - Staff, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 38)
  - Marshal Instructions, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 39)
  - Instructions to Student Procession Marshals, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 40)
  - Instructions for Faculty Procession Marshals, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 41)
  - Instructions for Marshals -- Entrance, Guest Seating, Live TV, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 42)
  - Coles Planning, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 43)
  - Commencement Ticket, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 44)
  - Board of Trustees Dinner, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 45)
  - Commencement Directory, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 46)
  - Program, Ephemera, Instructions, Planning and Post-Event Correspondence, 1991 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Program, Ephemera, Instructions, Planning and Post-Event Correspondence, 1992 (Box 81, Folder 11-16)
  - Programs, Planning Files, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 47-48)
  - Script -- President L. Jay Oliva, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 49)
  - Script, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 50)
  - Coles Rain Script, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 51)
  - Coles Rain Script -- President L. Jay Oliva, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 52)
  - Alumni Brunch, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 53)
  - Catering, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 54)
  - Romich Memos, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 55)
  - Requisitions, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 56)
  - Instructions for Students Procession Marshals, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 57)
  - Program, Planning Files, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 58-60)
  - Script -- Jops, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 61)
  - Script -- President L. Jay Oliva, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 62)
  - Script -- Abbreviated Park (Rain), 1993 (Box 41, Folder 63)
  - Script -- Snow Room (Rain), 1993 (Box 41, Folder 64)
  - Seating Marshals, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 65)
  - Procession Marshals, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 66)
  - Catering, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Set-up Memos, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Trustees Pre-Commencement Dinner, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Post-Commencement Mailing, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Script-Revised 5/12/93, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Scripts with Prologue, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Scripts -- Synopsis, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Information, Fliers, Forms, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 8-9)
  - Service Recording, May 13, 1993 (Box 54, Audiocassette 7_4_050 -- 7_4_051)
  - Instructions -- Faculty Procession Marshals, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 10)